LeeAnn Clayton,

a **UX/UI designer** with an affinity for storytelling and connecting with users. Experienced in intuitive creative solutions and research-backed designs. Capable of working in communication and developing social media assets and campaigns to connect businesses with their audiences.

UX/UI PROJECTS

Dimensions, Native Mobile App

CareerFoundry Case Study & View here

October 2021 — November 2021

Designed a sci-fi livestream app by conducting a competitive analysis, user interviews, A/B testing using Usability Hub, creating wireframes, a style guide by adhering to Material Design and iOS Guidelines and creating end-to-end prototypes.

Nomadic, Responsive Web App

CareerFoundry Case Study & View here

June 2021 — September 2021

Created a social hiking app by using AGILE to design the user experience (UX) in a series of sprints with interviews, market analysis, personas, and wireframe ideation using a mobile-first approach. Created a style guide and made informed user interaction (UI) decisions with user testing under the guidance of two senior designers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Digital Design Contractor

Tinyhood, Inc Online course service for new parents

April 2021 — August 2021

- Created engaging visuals for digital marketing channels such as social media, promo emails and online ads
- Helped develop visual language for new branding using A/B testing for informed design decisions across three social channels
- · Assisted in social media coordination publishing through Sprout Social

Freelance Graphic Designer

CBF Productions Live events & entertainment

July 2020 — January 2021

- Ideated creative content for digital marketing helping to grow the Instagram channel following 233% in 6 months
- Added and modified event information, prepared images and text for the website and social channels, edited videos for content

Graphic Design Intern

The Walt Disney Company Disney Parks, Experiences & Products

July 2019 — April 2020

- Assisted the design team with stakeholder design projects adherring to deadlines and milestones in project management system
- Headed Powerpoint template creation for internal teams
- Streamlined ad intake process for layout of the internal cast magazine to optimize production time

CONTACT

- Raleigh, North Carolina, USA (Open to Relocating)
- @ leeannbclayton@gmail.com
- (850) 512 5549
- lbclayton.com
- in /lbclayton
- Bē <u>/lbclayton</u>

SKILLS

Design

User Research, User Interface, User-Centered Design, Branding, Logo, Print, Digital, Wireframing, Personas, Style Guides, Iconography, Typography, Usability, Responsive Grids

Tools

Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, InDesign, After Effects, Figma, Atom

Prototyping

Adobe XD, Figma

Additional

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Google Analytics, Keynote, Powerpoint, A/B Testing, Social Media Coordination, Time Management

EDUCATION

User Interface Design Immersion + Frontend Web Specialization

April 2021 — February 2022

CareerFoundry

Intensive project-based training program with a focus on user research, user interface design, user experience design, motion interaction and frontend web development.

B.S. Graphic Design

August 2015 — May 2019 Illinois State University